He's not home alone.
The Vagrant is a comedy, horror, thriller film directed by Chris Walas.
A business man buys a house, but he has a hard time trying to
get rid of its previous tenant, a dirty bum.
Graham Krakowski, played by Bill Paxton.
Lt. Ralf Barfuss, played by Michael Ironside.
The Vagrant, played by Marshall Bell.
Edie Roberts, played by Mitzi Kapture.
Judy Dansig, played by Colleen Camp.
Doattie, played by Patrika Darbo.
The Vagrant is a 1992 comedy horror film directed by Chris Walas and executive
produced by Mel Brooks, through his Brooksfilms production company.
The film stars Bill Paxton as Graham Krakowski, a financial clerk who is being driven insane by a homeless man
(Marshall Bell) after moving into a new home across the street from where the homeless man had been squatting.
The film explores themes of trailer park, detective, paranoia, office, trial.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.